Guide to the Cleveland Robinson Papers WAG.006.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General and Political Files, 1960-1992.
  - King Center, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - King Center, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - King Center, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - King Center, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - King Center, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - King Center, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - King Center, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - King Center: Freedom Hall Campaign, 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - King Freedom Fund, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1985-1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: Federal Holiday Commission, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: Holiday, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: Holiday, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: New York State Commission, ca.1968, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: New York State Commission, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: New York State Commission, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: New York State Commission, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: New York State Commission, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: New York State Commission, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: New York State Commission, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: New York State Commission, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: New York State Commission (Financial Disclosure), 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: New York Support Group, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: Nobel Peace Prize and NYC Salute, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: Speeches and Writings, 1961-1968, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - King, Martin Luther, Sr., 1965-1977 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - La Luz, Jose, 1977-1980 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Labor Committee against Apartheid, 1983-1989 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Labor Law Reform, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Labor Research Association, 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Labor Research Association: Honors Cleveland Robinson, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Leland, Mickey, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Local 1199, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Management Futures, Inc, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Mandela Freedom Fund, 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Mandela, Nelson: New York Visit, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - March on Washington, Planning etc., 1962-1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - March on Washington: Twentieth Anniversary Mobilization, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - March on Washington: 25th Anniversary, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Medgar Evers College, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Merita Bread Co. Strike, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Militant: Interview with Cleveland Robinson, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Minimum Wage Campaign, 1962-1965 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Namibia, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - National Afro-American Labor Council, 1964, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - National Afro-American Labor Council, 1973, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - National Anti-Imperialist Movement in Solidarity with African Liberation, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1983-1986 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - NAACP, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - NAACP Special Contribution Fund, 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - National Campaign for Peace in the Middle East, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - National Lawyers Guild, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - National Mobilization for Justice and Peace in Central America and Southern Africa, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - National Rainbow Coalition, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - NY Anti-Apartheid Coordinating Council, undated, 1963, 1981-1985 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - NY Anti-Apartheid Coordinating Council, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - NY Anti-Apartheid Coordinating Council, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - NY Anti-Apartheid Coordinating Council, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - NY Anti-Apartheid Welcome Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - NYC Commission on Human Rights: Congratulations, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - NYC Mayor's Office, 1986-1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - New York Labor Committee against Apartheid, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - New York Labor Committee against Apartheid, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - New York Labor Committee against Apartheid, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - New York Labor Committee against Apartheid, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - New York State Coalition for Social and Economic Justice, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - NYS Department of Labor, 1979-1988 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - NY State Government, 1984, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - NY State Governor's Office, 1983-1992 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Phelps Dodge Strike, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Philippines, 1984-1985, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Police Brutality, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Political: Campaigns, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Political: General, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Political: General, undated, 1977, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Political: General, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Political: General, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Political: General, 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Progressive Alliance, 1977-1980 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Roberts, Lillian, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Robeson, Paul, 1973, 1978, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Robinson, Cleveland: Biographical/ Personal, 1965-1992 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Rustin, Bayard, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Schappes, Morris, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Schomburg Center (New York Public Library), 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Serounya and Son: Demonstration, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - South Africa: General, 1983-1985 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - South Africa: General, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - South Africa: General, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - South Africa: General, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - South Africa: General, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - South Africa: General, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - South Africa: Solidarity Conference, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference, 1962-1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference, 1984-1991 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Spock, Benjamin, M.D., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Television Appearances, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Thomas, Clarence, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Transafrica, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Transafrica, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Unions: Foreign, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Unions: General, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Unions: General, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Unions: General, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Unions: General, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Unions: General, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - United States Congress, 1969-1987 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - United States Congress, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Senate, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Urban League, 1983-1990 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Vietnam Moratorium, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Von Luther, Sidney, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Voter Education Project, 1971- 1974 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Voting Rights Act: Anniversary, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Wells Fargo Operators Union, undated, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Photographs, correspondence, and audiotape, 1959-1991 (Box 18, Folder 1-6, Box Shared Tamiment 004, Cassette (Just Say No to Drugs))